来个纸杯蛋糕吗?
Care for a cupcake?
我们的新的室外座位区
Well, our new outdoor seating area
就如保拉・迪恩在NBA现场一样倍受冷落
is about as popular as Paula Deen at an NBA game.
保拉・迪恩: 美国明星厨师
我们还要在这里坐多久?
How much longer do we have to be out here?
我们好冷
We are cold.
超级冷
So, so cold.
我都能看到呼出的空气
I can see my breath.
我的鸡鸡冻得戳到胸口了
And my boys are up by my rib cage.
我都能闻到他的口臭
I can smell his breath.
我的鸡鸡被冻得跟年轻时一样硬了
And my boys are up by where my boys used to be.
这些顾客根本帮不上忙
And these customers aren't helping.
我们怎么会以为Han坐在门口
How could we have thought a strong Han presence
能增加蛋糕销量的?
would make it more popular?
Max 我就说了吧
Max, in hindsight,
不重新花钱去买取暖灯
it feels like us not springing for those heat lamps
是个错误的决定
was a bad call.
是你自己觉得吧?
Uh, you think?
各位 为了保暖 我刚撒了点尿
Guys, I just peed a little to keep warm.
我也撒了点尿
Well, I peed a little
因为我没办法了
'cause I had no choice.
好吧 他们黏在长椅上了
Great, they're stuck to the bench.
去把挡风玻璃铲拿过来
Go get the windshield scraper.
破产姐妹花 第四季第10集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 酱油影  时间轴: 。沫
校对: 桃茜茜
翻译: 酱油影 猫呗 奥利奥 落寞卷菜
你在看"我们"周刊吗 Earl?
Reading Us Weekly, Earl?
噢 "明星 和平凡人一样"
Ooh, "Stars. They're just like us."
如果他们真和我们一样 那怎么没有
Well, if they're just like us, where's the picture
他们把内裤翻过来重复穿的照片?
of them turning their underwear inside out?
Caroline把这个留在了男厕所里
Caroline left it in the men's room.
当我把这话说出来时
And as I said that out loud,
我就意识到我肯定是错入了女厕所
I realized that I must have been in the ladies' room.
我眼睛不好 Max
I can't see, Max.
Max 我有个让人兴奋消息!
Max, I've got some exciting news!
我发过誓 在看过最后一部"夺宝奇兵"之后
Eh, I vowed I'd never get excited about anything again
我不会再为任何事兴奋了
after that last Indiana Jones.
我在"雪丽清单"网上找到了两盏折扣取暖灯
I found us two discount heat lamps on Sherry's list.
它和分类广告网相似 但降低了
It's like Craigslist, but without the high probability
被某个疯狂医学生杀掉的风险
of being murdered by a deranged medical student.
那些取暖灯?
And about those lamps?
才不要
Uh, no.
我们不必再担心室外生意啦
We can't worry about our outdoor business.
因为店里都快没生意了
We barely have an indoor business.
照你这个态度 我们再也不会有生意了
And we never will, with that attitude.
我再求你一次:
I'm gonna ask you one more time:
拜托去听听我们在垃圾里找到的
please listen to those Tony Robbins tapes
托尼・罗宾斯的励志磁带吧
we found in the garbage.
姑娘们
Well, girls,
明天就是我盼了三年的
tomorrow's the day I've been looking forward to
大好日子
for three years.
你要去洗牙了吗?
You're getting your teeth cleaned?
抱歉 那是我们盼望着的事情
Sorry, that's what's we've been looking forward to.
我要搬去和Sophie同居
I'm moving in with Sophie.
从现在开始 不出家门我也能上辣妹了
From now on, the booty call is coming from inside the house.
我只是无意听到的
I couldn't help but overhear.
这么远都能听到?
From way back there?
你的耳朵真该给你的全身做个身残志坚的演讲
Your ears should give a pep talk to the other parts of your body.
Oleg 如果你搬家需要帮手的话
And, Oleg, if you need any help with the move,
我可以去帮你忙吗?
might I offer my services?
我的教练Skylar说我有肌肉了
My trainer Skylar says I'm getting ripped.
是啊 你是Skylar给坑了吧
Yeah, ripped off by Skylar.
谢了 Han
Thanks, Han.
作为小小的回报
And as a bit of a payback,
我今晚回来时会洗手的
I'll wash my hands back here tonight.
一会儿见 邻居们
See you later, neighbors.
Oleg要搬过来?
Oleg's moving in?
这是我遇上最糟糕的事情
This is the worst thing that's ever happened to me.
比损失了20亿还糟糕
And I lost $2 billion.
有什么问题? 这都是好消息
What is the problem? This is all good news.
Sophie和Oleg相爱了
Sophie and Oleg are in love.
没错!
Yeah!
他们就会在我们的楼梯上
And they'll be in love
在我们的大厅里
on our stairs,
在洗衣房
in our hallway,
所有的平面上相亲相爱
and on every surface of the laundry room.
再说 你懂什么爱 单身"相亲"汉?
What do you know about love anyway, Christian Single?
我知道上帝为我准备了妹子
I know Jesus has a girl for me.
他必须准备
He has to.
我在相亲网上花了400刀
I'm $400 deep into that damn website.
听着 我们必须制定条约
Look, we just make a pact
无论楼上 楼梯上
that no matter what happens upstairs,
还是洗衣房里发生了什么事
or on the stairs or in the laundry room,
绝对不能让他们进我们的公寓
we don't invite it into our apartment.
各位好!
Hey, everybody!
外面在下倾盆大羊
It's raining cats and goats out there.
你是想说"倾盆大雨"吗?
Don't you mean "cats and dogs"?
一走进门就被纠正错误的感觉真好
Oh, it's so nice to be corrected as you walk in the door.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, baby.
你能相信24小时内 我们就要活在罪恶里吗?
Can you believe in 24 hours we'll be living in sin?
别担心
Oh, don't worry.
我父母不知道
My parents don't know.
我明晚要开个晚宴来庆祝
I'm having a dinner party tomorrow night to celebrate.
还有个原因 我有15磅牛肉
And also because I have 15 pounds of beef
快要变质了
that's about to go bad.
Max Caroline 你们来吗?
So, Max, Caroline, are you in?
Sophie 其实我们很忙...
Actually, Sophie, we're busy...
我们会去的
We'll be there.
只要有牛肉 我就会去
If there's beef involved, I'm involved.
你忘了我们刚才制定的条约吗?
What happened to the pact we just made?
我真不愿告诉你...
I hate to tell you this...
要在你和牛肉间选的话
if it comes down to you or beef,
我永远会选牛肉
I'm always going beef.
是"雪丽清单"的雪丽发来的
That was Sherry from Sherry's list.
她非要我那么叫她
She makes you call her that.
她说如果我们能自己去提货
She said she's consider charging us $150
她可以考虑取暖灯只收我们150刀
if we pick up the heat lamps themselves.
你打扰了我看"坐劣质高脚凳的婴儿"视频
And I'm charging you with three counts of interrupting
我要罚你三倍的金额
this "Baby in a Faulty High Chair" video.
有人摔倒了!
Someone fell in real life!
你说在你手上的
You told me you had it.
我说了我没拿
I said I didn't have it.
是Oleg和Han在搬家
It's Oleg and Han moving in.
离门远点!
Get away from the door!
Han能从门缝里看到你的脚
Han will see your feet under the door.
这正对他的视平线啊
They're right at his eye level.
简直就是恐怖片... 电锯惊魂3
This is like a horror movie... Saw III.
因为Han弯腰的时候
Because when Han bent over,
我看到他露出的3英寸屁股沟
I saw 3 inches of his crack.
所以你啥都看到了?
So you saw his whole crack?
后退!
Step away!
开门 Max
Open the door, Max.
我要杀了Han
I'm about to kill Han,
我知道你想看的
and I know you're gonna want to see that.
该死! 他说得对
Damn it! He's right.
这服装挺可爱的 Han
Cute outfit, Han.
穿的和"雷霆猛男"里面的
Like one of those male strippers
脱衣舞男一样
from "No Thunder From Down Under."
这箱子太重了
This is so heavy.
Oleg 你这里面装了什么呀?
Oleg, what do you have in here?
袜子!
Socks!
不是吧 Han
Really, Han,
你的两条胳膊只是用来装饰的啊
It's like your arms are only there for decoration.
公平来说 Oleg的袜子里
To be fair, Oleg's socks
也许装着他千千万万的子孙后代
probably have some pretty heavy loads in them.
Oleg 你把你的垃圾都堆这干嘛?
Oleg, what is all your junk doing out here?
我确实是听到妹子的尖叫声了吗
Do I actually smell girls screaming?
我把东西搬上去 Sophie说了句"我不要"
I bring things up, Sophie says "No,"
我就得把这些东西都搬回去
I bring them right back down.
这烂楼里就没个电梯吗?
Is there no elevator up in this bitch?
Oleg 你忘了你的画
Oleg, you forgot your painting,
这也是明确被拒绝的东西之一
and this one's a definite "No."
Sophie 我还没听到你说一句"我要"呢
Sophie, I haven't gotten a "Yes" yet,
除了咱俩在厕所洗水池上速战速决那会儿
aside from the quickie we had up against the bathroom sink.
哪是什么速战速决
Not such a quickie.
他们把我锁在外面 我只得在货车里吃午饭
They locked me out and I had to eat my lunch in the truck.
那我租一辆货车又有什么意义?
Then what was the point of me renting a moving truck?
除了可以倚着车厢壁完成高难度动作的一炮
I mean, besides the rough sex we had up against the sides?
那次他们把我锁在车外 扔在路上了
They locked me outside on the side of the road for that one.
好了 我们该回去了
Okay, well, we have to go back in.
今晚的牛肉全餐见
See you tonight at the beef-a-thon.
不 Oleg
No, Oleg.
也许是我做得不公平
Maybe I'm being unfair.
这些东西都是你喜欢的
I mean, you have all this stuff that you like,
而她们又有个公寓
and they have an apartment.
把它们放进去吧
Put it in there.
喂Sophie!
Sophie!
8点见!
I'll see you at 8:00!
你们说呢 妹子们?
So what do you say, girls?
绝对不行
Absolutely not...
可以
Yes.
Max 我答应自有我的道理
Max, there's a method to my madness.
Oleg 可以让我们说几句话吗?
Oleg, will you excuse us a second?
你可以帮帮Han拿箱子
And maybe help Han with that box.
站在那堆短裤里面 他都要得疝气了
In those shorts, I can actually see a hernia happening.
我还以为我们不牵涉其中的!
I thought we weren't getting involved!
如果我们帮Oleg的忙
If we help Oleg out,
他会把那辆货车借给我们
he'll let us use the moving truck
去运我们的加热灯啊
to pick up our heat lamps.
我已经说了"我不要"
I already said "No" to those.
但是我们说好了啊!
But we just talked about it!
我没在听啊!
I wasn't listening!
那个小宝宝可是把脸摔进了土豆泥里了!
That baby fell face-down into mashed potatoes.
但是你答应了这个牛肉全餐
But you said "Yes" to the dinner party,
所以你要吃你的肉 那我要我的热
so if you get your meat, I get my heat.
别以为你说得押韵我就同意了
Just because you rhyme doesn't make it okay.
而且那句话肯定是蕾哈娜对克里斯・布朗说的
And I'm pretty sure that's what Rihanna said to Chris Brown.
我们要去哪里跟这妹子见面买加热灯啊
Where are we meeting this chick with the heat lamps?
自从计划生育在新泽西实施起
I haven't gone this far for something I didn't want
我就没有为自己不想要的东西而跑过这么远
since Planned Parenthood moved to New Jersey.
喂!
Hello!
我在后面都要晕车了
I'm getting truck sick back here.
人人皆认为我的开车技术烂 你比我还烂
You're a worse driver than people assume I am.
快点! 快点!
Come on! Come on!
我们快要赶不上晚餐啦!
We're gonna be late to dinner!
有人愿意和我玩剪刀石头布吗
Would any of you be interested in playing
赢的人就可以坐前面
rock-paper-scissors for a seat up front?
不行!
No!
妹子们 我可以问你们一个感情问题吗
Girls, can I ask you a relationship question?
不行!
No!
而且 我们哪会了解什么感情问题
And besides, what would we know about relationships?
就像你去问唐纳德・特朗普
That's like asking Donald Trump
有什么好发型师一样
for the name of a good hairstylist.
她到底是怎么回事?
I mean, what's the deal with her?
她让我搬过去
She asks me to move in,
但是连一副画都不能带过去?
and then won't even let me have my painting?
Sophie连奶牛都买了一头
I mean, Sophie already bought the cow.
她也许还会允许那奶牛拉屎
She might as well let the cow's crap in.
所以你的意思是我有理
So you're saying I'm right.
不 不 但我确实觉得...
No, no, but I do think...
不 你才不觉得
No, you don't think,
你纯粹就是没话找话说罢了
or your mouth wouldn't be moving right now.
我只是说
I'm just saying,
他有权把他的东西搬进
he has the right to move some of his stuff
Sophie公寓 并从我们公寓搬出去
into Sophie's apartment and out of ours.
说起他的东西
Speaking of his stuff,
这盒子里面有个东西
there's something in a box back here
正震动... 哦 停下了
is humming, and... oh, it stopped.
哦 又开始了
Oh, it started again.
这玩意可是有着仿真的人类嘴部
That's my lifelike mouth with authentic jaw action.
Oleg 看路!
Oleg, watch the road!
我真心不想听到"仿真嘴"
这种东西
The last words I hear can't be "lifelike mouth."
你这里相当不错啊 Sophie
Everything looks very nice, Sophie.
是嘛
Yeah, see,
在其他客人来到之前我不打算说话
I'm not gonna talk until the other guests arrive.
我要把热情的待客之道留给真正的贵宾
I got to save my hostess sparkle for the real guests.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, baby.
你究竟死哪儿去了
Where the hell have you been?
这待客之道真是热情的要命
That was a pretty loud sparkle.
Sophie 大伙儿迟到全怪我
It's my fault we're late, Sophie...
没事 坐下吧
It's okay. Just sit down.
你想不想知道我刚刚...
Don't you want to know what I was...
不想
No, really.
我这里的炖牛肉
I got a pot roast over here
比你有趣多了
that's a hell of a lot more interesting.
Max 感谢上帝你来了
Max, thank God you're here.
刚才的安静真是太尴尬了
There was so much awkward silence,
我还得假装接到一条香蕉的来电
I pretended I got a phone call from a banana.
我得去厕所冲一冲
I'm gonna take a quick shower.
Oleg 晚饭做好了
Oh, Oleg, Dinner is ready.
没时间让你去打飞机了啊
You don't have time to run down to the "Y" now.
不 我是说要在这里冲个澡
No, I meant I would shower here.
这里...
Here...
用我的浴室?
In my bathroom?
呃...
Uh...
是啊
Yeah.
我都搬来住了
I live here now.
哦 对啊
Oh, yeah.
还真是呢
That's right.
我要想象一下
Imagine that.
嘿 Oleg 你不如过来
Hey, Oleg, why don't you just come over here
坐Earl旁边?
and sit next to Earl?
因为他年纪大了 嗅觉没那么灵敏的
Because he's old and I'm sure his smeller is shot.
Sophie你一定要出本"待客之道"的书
Sophie, you really must write a "how to entertain" book.
要上菜了
Here we go:
金克斯基姥姥的招牌炖肉
Grandma Chinkski's pot roast.
看起来真可口
This looks amazing.
我特喜欢在冬天吃根菜
I love a root vegetable in the winter.
可以只以我为中心吗?
Can it ever just be about me?
# 小啊小牛肉 #
# Beef, beef, beef #
# 牛啊牛啊肉 #
# B-beef, b-beef, beef #
咋了 我在唱自己的牛肉歌啊
What? That's my beef song.
我想敬Sophie一杯
I'd like to make a toast to Sophie.
真是贴心
Oh, that's sweet.
但别用那酒杯
But not with that glass.
那是金斯基姥姥的玻璃杯
That's Grandma Chinski's crystal.
宝贝 我正在给你敬酒呢
Baby, I was in the middle of a toast.
真是不好意思 可...
Oh, I'm sorry, but...
这些杯子是我的最爱啊!
those are my favorite thing!
是金斯基姥姥用两个傻表兄换来的
Grandma Chinski traded two of my slow cousins for those.
说来好笑
Well, you know, it's funny.
我也有个最爱
I have a favorite thing too.
要不 我去拿来给你看看?
In fact, why don't I just go and get it?
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
马上就要见着洛尼・安德森了!
I'm about to meet Loni Anderson!
洛尼・安德森 美国女星
有人能帮我提下叉子吗?
Can someone help me lift up my fork?
搬趟东西我的双臂已经酸得不行了
My arms are still sore from the move.
张开嘴
Open up.
换你们来喂Han吧
Someone else has to feed Han.
他刚刚舔到了我的小指
He just licked my pinky.
Earl 在那干啥呢?
Earl, what are you doing over there?
在陪节奏布鲁斯歌手闲逛呢
Just hanging out with R&B sensation,
大名鼎鼎的大麻玛丽
Mary J.-juana.
好极了
Oh, good.
你这心态最适合去喂一个30岁的男人了
So you're in the right mind-set to hand-feed a 30-year-old man.
哦 别别别别
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
我估计波兰人就这么说"不"的
I think that's Polish for "No."
啊哈 就是这个 Sophie
Uh... huh. Yes, Sophie.
这是我的油画 说错了 我们的油画
It's my painting. Excuse me... our painting.
现在要挂在我们的墙上
And it's going up on our wall.
是我的问题呢
Is it me,
还是这派对的气氛相当紧张啊?
or is this party tense as hell?
我觉得Sophie和Oleg合不来啊
I don't think Sophie and Oleg are gonna make it.
啊哦... 我大声说出来了吗?
Uh... oh. Am I talking out loud right now?
早跟你说了 我不要这东西挂在这里
I told you, I don't want that thing in here.
我不明白 不就是幅油画嘛
I don't understand. It's just a painting.
有什么大不了的?
What's so bad about it?
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
不错吧?
Nice, huh?
我亲手画的
I did it myself.
我的个人肖像
It's a paint-by-numbers.
你是想说普京肖像吧
You mean it's a Putin-by-numbers.
为什么上面乳头这么大?
Why are his nipples so big?
我觉得不会太大啊
They don't seem that big to me.
哦 我已经嗨得受不了
Oh, I am too high for this.
我还不够嗨呢
I'm not high enough.
在我那 大乳头意味着财富和权力
In my culture, big nipples mean power and wealth.
在我这 大乳头意味着
In our culture, big nipples means,
"麻烦穿上衣服再去泳池"
"Wears a t-shirt in the pool."
挂好了
There.
我挺喜欢的
I like it.
给这房间带来种莫名的格调
Adds a certain something to the room.
每面墙都得挂上乳头
Every wall needs nipples.
那样男人们就知道看哪了
So a guy knows where to look.
谢谢你的主意 Caroline
Thank you for telling me to do this, Caroline.
她的主意?
She did?
我想站起来溜走 但我双腿发软
I'd get up and run, but my legs are like taffy.
说真的
Seriously,
你居然让他把那玩意儿挂起来?
you told him to hang that thing up?
说实在的 我当时还没见着那油画
In fairness, I had not seen the painting
所以我才这么建议他的
when I suggested something like that.
我是说 我明白
I mean, I get it.
这确实很霸气
It's gorgeous.
但这跟屋内的装潢不搭
But it doesn't go with the decor.
什么?
What?
所以你要丢掉这幅霸气的里外两用的挂像?
Is it throwing off this gorgeous outdoor-indoor swing?
再说小心我拿餐刀砍你!
I'll cut you with the carving knife!
谁也别砍谁
Nobody is cutting anyone.
特别是我
Especially not me.
你不懂吗?
Do you never learn?
赶紧像我这样用餐巾包住牛肉
Just put some beef in your napkin like I did,
然后赶紧离开这里
and let's get out of here.
Sophie是你叫我搬来住的
Sophie, you asked me to move in.
现在可好? 我搬进来了
Guess what? I moved in.
是 是我叫你搬来的
Yes, I asked you to move in,
但没说带上这乳头大得出奇的普京像
but not with big weird-nipple Putin.
那多大的乳头算正常?
Well, how big are nipples supposed to be?
因为... 算了
'Cause... never mind.
那你现在又发什么疯?
And what's your problem anyway?
我都给你挪了个抽屉
I gave you a drawer.
就这个!
This!
大家快看 这就是我的抽屉
This is my drawer, everybody.
这么小有什么用?
What good is this?
连个堵嘴球都装不下
I can't even get one of my ball gags in there.
你说要个抽屉 这不给了你个抽屉!
You asked for a drawer, I gave you a drawer!
再说谁用得上一打堵嘴球?
And who needs 12 ball gags anyway?
哦 现在你又不喜欢戴堵嘴球了?
Oh, so now you don't like ball gags?
你个女人算什么?
Who are you, lady?
我告诉你我就是...
I'll tell you who I am...
我就是把这普京像丢进垃圾桶的女人!
I'm the lady who's "Putin" this is the trash!
你丢那个我就砸了这个
You trash that, I'll trash this.
哦 别
Oh, no.
哦 你是觉得你能摔
Oh, you think you're gonna break
金斯基姥姥的玻璃杯是吧?
one of Grandma Chinski's glasses?
没门 就算是摔 也是老娘摔!
No, if anyone's gonna break one, it's gonna be me!
这让我想起了我第二段婚姻的前半段
This reminds me of the first half of my second marriage,
和我第三段婚姻的后半段
and the second half of my third marriage.
Sophie我受够了
Sophie, I'm done.
正如你第一次约会时跟我说
And as you said to me on our first date,
"我不知道自己受得了多少"
"I don't know how much more of this I can take."
多么有趣的聚会啊
Fun party.
一点都不尴尬
Not awkward at all.
但是我真该走了
I should get going though.
我明天还得早起... 去啥来着?
Got to be up early for... what's a thing?
教会?
Church?
牛肉 牛肉 牛肉?
Beef, beef, beef?
牛 牛肉 牛肉 牛肉 牛肉?
B-beef, beef, beef, beef?
昨天的聚会真是不好意思啊
Sorry about that dinner party last night.
我有点失控了
It kind of got away from me a little bit.
你们能早起帮我把Oleg的东西运回去
But I really appreciate you getting up early
我实在是太感激了
and helping me move Oleg's stuff back.
我只是觉得我也有错...
I just actually feel like this is a little bit my fault...
说真的!
Seriously!
可以让我做焦点吗?
Can it ever just be about me?
嘿 唔
Hey, um,
我们要把他的东西运到哪儿去?
where are we taking his stuff anyway?
我觉得即使是好意 也无法接受
I don't think goodwill will take a love seat
那张沾满爱液的性爱椅子
that's actually covered in love.
呃 我在想
Well, I was thinking,
你们也知道 我和Oleg的关系
you know, since Oleg and I
确实不一般
really did have something special,
所以我想着我干脆
I was thinking I would just take his stuff
把他的东西丢到河里得了
and dump it down by the river.
好吧 我一定要说出来...
Okay, I'm just gonna say it...
Sophie 让Oleg把那幅破画
Sophie, would it kill you
挂在墙上 会要了你的命吗?
to just let Oleg hang the damn painting?
天啊 你就这样
So what, you just park the truck
把货车停在高速公路上?
in the middle of the Van Wyck Expressway?
你就不能受点教训吗?
Do you never learn?
我差点连租车公司的地毯都吃下去了
I almost ate Rent-A-Truck floor mat.
Caroline 你把话说清楚...
Caroline, you get this straight...
是Oleg的错
Oleg was wrong.
普京乳头实在是太大了
And those nipples were way too big.
太尴尬了
This is awkward.
你在卡车里?
You're in the truck?
不 是你在我的房间里
No, you're in my apartment.
我觉得我们被撞了
I think something hit us.
你们只是需要接受配偶治疗
You guys just need some couples therapy.
我来帮你们调解吧
I'll mediate it,
我曾经给自己做过治疗
since I've had therapy myself.
虽然我没有另一半 但希望在未来有
Not as a couple, but hopefully someday.
我只想坐在这等拖车
I'm just sitting here waiting for the tow truck to come.
你的脖子还好吗 Max?
How's your neck, Max?
还好
Not so bad.
被第一辆车撞歪的脖子
The second car that hit us kind of knocked
又被第二辆车给撞回原位了
what the first car knocked out of place back in place.
我先来
I'll start.
这个女人就是一个骗子
This woman is a fraud and a liar.
好吧 呃
Okay, well,
要欧普拉式的真情 少点杰里・斯普林格式的讽刺
we need a little more Oprah, a little less Jerry Springer.
嘿 别说杰里・斯普林格的坏话
Hey, don't dis Springer.
他们的绿屋子里的零食很好吃
They have great snacks in the green room.
你上过杰里・斯普林格的节目?
You were on Jerry Springer?
没错 我参加了"我讨厌我室友"
Yeah, I was on "I hate my roommate
但不知道怎么告诉她"那期节目
and I don't know how to tell her."
Oleg和我说不清楚的
Oleg and I are not gonna talk this thing out.
如果你想浪费时间
If you want to waste your time,
就去市中心的中学教书吧
go teach in an inner city high school.
你知道吗? 为了更有效地治疗
You know what? Even better...
我来帮Oleg说话
I'll do the talking for Oleg.
哦 那么 Max... 你来帮我 好吗Max?
Oh, then, Max... you be me, okay, Max?
呃... 我不知道是不是...
Oh... I don't know if...
你还想不想要剩下的牛肉了?
Do you want the rest of the beef, or not?
这个家伙是个混蛋 那些画应该被丢掉
This guy is a bum, and the painting has to go.
简直太蠢了
It's stupid.
非常 非常好 Max
Really, really good, Max
但是下一次 你的腰得挺直 嗯 没错
but next time just arch your back a little, and, yeah.
好的
Yeah.
好吧 你来当我
Okay, you be me.
不 我不要受你勃起的老二威胁
No, I don't feel like getting a threatening erection right now.
但是 当人们住在一起时
But I will say, anytime people move in together,
就得相互妥协
it's a compromise.
看看Max...
Look at Max...
当我需要安身之所 她还让我保留了自己的马
when I needed a place to stay, she let me have my horse.
这么说吧 我在斯普林格的节目也这么说的
Let me just say... and I brought this up on Springer...
我是为了那匹马才让你住的
I only let you in because of the horse.
还有就是我终于不再反对
And I finally stopped putting up a fight
同意让Max在街上裸奔
and let Max walk around naked.
这是什么时候的事?
When did that happen?
明天
Tomorrow.
哦 Oleg
Oh, Oleg,
我不想阻止你在街上裸奔
I wouldn't want you to give up walking around naked.
只要你别坐在白色的东西上面就行
I mean, as long as you don't sit down on anything white.
有道理
Makes sense.
没人喜欢在椅子上留下个巧克力色的印迹
Nobody likes a chocolate starfish on an ottoman.
Sophie得分
Point, Sophie.
哈! 我赢了 看见没!
Ha! I'm winning, everybody!
呃 这是治疗性谈话
Well, it's therapy.
没有输赢
There are no winners and losers.
听起来像是输家说的话
Sounds like something a loser would say.
你知道吗 Oleg
You know, Oleg,
这不是这些破画的问题
this isn't about that silly little painting.
只是 呃
It's just, uh,
在这么短的时间里发生了这么多变化...
a lot of change in a short amount of time...
让我感到害怕
I'm so scared.
Sophie宝贝啊
Sophie,
只要有你 其他东西我都不在乎
I don't care about my stuff, as long as I have you.
我们做了什么?
What did we just do?
我们把他们分开 现在却又让他们在一起
We had them apart, and now we just put them back together.
你的功劳
You did that.
你不知道在什么时候闭嘴
You don't know when to butt out.
杰里说的
Jerry's words.